<idea-plugin>
    <id>ObsidianSunset</id>
    <version>2.0.1</version>
    <name>Obsidian Sunset Theme</name>
    <category>UI</category>

    <vendor email="l.czerniawski@icloud.com" url="https://github.com/lczerniawski">Łukasz Czerniawski</vendor>

    <idea-version since-build="231" until-build="251.*"/>
    
    <description><![CDATA[
    <b>Obsidian Sunset</b> is a dark and colorful theme for Visual Studio Code that enhances the readability and aesthetics of your code.
    The theme is inspired by the colors of the sky during sunset, with orange, yellow, purple, and blue hues. It features a deep black background with vibrant syntax highlighting in orange, green, blue, and grey.
    Whether you are coding in C#, Python, JS, or any other language, Obsidian Sunset will make your code stand out with its rich contrast and elegant design.
    Obsidian Sunset is ideal for developers who prefer a dark theme that is not too harsh on the eyes, but still provides a clear and pleasing visual experience.
    <br/>
    <br/>

    <b>Why another theme?</b>
    <br/>
    <br/>
    The inception of this theme is rooted in my personal desire to have a single theme that is versatile across all programming languages I use.
    <ul>
        <li>
            Often, a theme that complements C# well may not be as visually coherent with Python.
        </li>
        <li>
            Background brightness of many themes is another issue; they are either too bright, causing eye strain, or too dark, making it difficult to view the screen in daylight.
        </li>
        <li>
            Lastly, a significant concern is the lack of color differentiation between various language components such as variables, properties, and functions. In many VS Code themes, these elements are often colored identically, making it challenging to quickly scan the code and distinguish between them.
        </li>
    </ul>

    <br/>
    With this theme, I aim to address all these issues and provide a visually pleasing, versatile, and user-friendly coding environment that enhances readability and productivity.
  ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <h3>[2.0.1] - 13.08.2024</h3>
    <h4>Changed</h4>
    Bumped idea-version

    <h3>[2.0.0] - 11.08.2024</h3>
    <h4>Added</h4>
    New color of theme with blue accents.
    <br/>
    <b>IMPORTANT</b> After this update you will have to re-select theme from theme picker, as names were adjusted.

    <h3>[1.0.0] - 10.03.2024</h3>
    Initial release of the theme.
  ]]></change-notes>


    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <themeProvider id="ObsidianSunsetOrange" path="/theme/ObsidianSunsetOrange.theme.json"/>
        <themeProvider id="ObsidianSunsetBlue" path="/theme/ObsidianSunsetBlue.theme.json"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>